http://www.cheaphumidors.com/pages/privacy-policy

Cigar Humidors 101
Does a Humidor Come Pre-Humidified?
[VIDEO] How To Set Up Your New Humidor
[VIDEO] What is a Cigar Capacity Rating?
[View All Articles...]
CIGAR CUTTER INFORMATION
7 Best Guillotine Cigar Cutters
[INFOGRAPHIC] How to Use Different Types of Cigar Cutters
[INFOGRAPHIC] Cigar Cutting 101
[View All Articles...]
HYGROMETER INFORMATION
How Do Analog Hygrometers Work?
Which Is Better: A Digital Or Analog Hygrometer?
Humidor Setup: How to Calibrate Your Hygrometer
[View All Articles...]
[VIDEO] Soft vs Torch Flame Lighters
[View All Articles...]
Cigar Humidors 101
Does a Humidor Come Pre-Humidified?
[VIDEO] How To Set Up Your New Humidor
[VIDEO] What is a Cigar Capacity Rating?
[View All Articles...]
CIGAR CUTTER INFORMATION
7 Best Guillotine Cigar Cutters
[INFOGRAPHIC] How to Use Different Types of Cigar Cutters
[INFOGRAPHIC] Cigar Cutting 101
[View All Articles...]
HYGROMETER INFORMATION
How Do Analog Hygrometers Work?
Which Is Better: A Digital Or Analog Hygrometer?
Humidor Setup: How to Calibrate Your Hygrometer
[View All Articles...]
[VIDEO] Soft vs Torch Flame Lighters
[View All Articles...]
Privacy Policy & Terms of Service
This privacy policy sets out how CheapHumidors.com uses and protects any information that you give CheapHumidors.com when you use this website. CheapHumidors.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. CheapHumidors.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences, and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at sales@cheaphumidors.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 217 Hobbs St #106 Tampa, FL 33619.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Children
CheapHumidors.com does not sell products for purchase by anyone under the age of eighteen. All products purchased at CheapHumidors.com must use a credit card where the purchaser or authorized signer is over the age of eighteen. We will not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children we know to be under the age of eighteen.
No Absolute Safeguards
Although we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your information, transmissions on the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Accordingly, we assume no responsibility or liability for disclosure of any of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access or other causes beyond our reasonable control.
Third Party Communication
In an effort to enhance your shopping experience, we may use your contact and demographic information we have collected through our website, surveys, or other data gathering methods to send you news, offers and e-mails from some of our partners. All of these messages allow you to opt-out at any time.
As a part of our business relationships, we may from time to time have banner or link redirects to a third party accessible from the CheapHumidors.com Site. Any transactions that occur between you and a third party are strictly between you and the third party and are not the responsibility of CheapHumidors.com. We do not control the privacy policies of our advertisers or other third parties that have Web sites linked to the Site. If you click on an advertisement or link, the privacy policies of the Web site that you link to will govern the use of your information by that Web site's operator. We assume no responsibility or liability for the actions of such third parties with respect to their use of your information or otherwise.
Sale of our Company
As our company grows, there is a possibility that we could be sold to another company. In the event that we are acquired by another company or a significant portion of our assets is sold to another company, all of the customer information including both financial records and consumer information that we have collected may be transferred to the new company.
Review, Request Changes or Opt Out
If you do not wish to receive announcements or special offers from us or third parties, you can unsubscribe from receiving e-mail communications regarding news, exclusive offers and reminders.
Acceptance of Our Privacy Policy
If you use the Site, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and we will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the Site. Use of this site is when this privacy effective date begins. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Site after we either personally notify you or generally post such changes on the site will constitute your acceptance of those changes.
Disclaimer
We're very sorry when this happens. Our intention is to have accurate descriptions that represent the items offered. Sometimes the problem comes from a mistake in data entry. Other times, the manufacturer has changed the product and we were not notified or data from our suppliers may not be 100% accurate. We do our best to have everything correct, but there are too many items to make any guarantees. As with every other catalog and online publication, we are not responsible for typographical errors. If you become aware of this situation we would appreciate you notifying us.
When an error is found, we will do what we can to correct the situation. There are times when products are not available or the item description is completely wrong and the only option is to apologize and refund your money. Manufacturers make changes in production and discontinue items. Certain items may not be available regardless of how badly you would like it to be so. We regret any errors on the website and thank you for your understanding if one is encountered.
